A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Photographs FA738
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General, Program, and Project Photographs, 3
  - Economic Development and Administration (EDA), 3_2
    - Transferability of Military Training, 1965 (Box 79, Folder 1300)
    - University of Western Ontario - School of Business Administration, 1964 (Box 79, Folder 1301)
    - Wharton School, 1961 (Box 79, Folder 1302)
  - Education and Research (E&R), 3_3
    - Alternative Schools, Berkeley, CA (TIME and Newsweek articles), 1972-1973 (Box 79, Folder 1303)
    - Atlanta University, 1953 (Box 79, Folder 1304)
    - Education, 1960s-1970s (Box 80, Folder 1305)
      Misc. general photographs
    - Border College Consortium Meeting, Brownsville, Texas, 1979 (Box 80, Folder 1306)
    - Brown University, Breakthrough in Teacher Training Program, 1960 (Box 80, Folder 1307)
    - Business Practices at Predominantly Negro Colleges - Dillard University, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 1308)
    - Catskill Area Project in Small School Design, 1960 (Box 80, Folder 1309)
    - Colorado College, 1965 (Box 80, Folder 1310)
    - Columbia University Demonstrations, Samuel I. Coleman and students, 1968 (Box 80, Folder 1311)
    - Columbia University School of Journalism - Training Minorities for Media, 1968 (Box 80, Folder 1312)
    - Community Junior Colleges, St. Louis, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 1313)
    - Educational Facilities Laboratories (EFL), 1965 (Box 80, Folder 1314)
    - Educational Facilities Laboratories (EFL), 1966 (Box 80, Folder 1315)
    - Education Improvement Program, Durham North Carolina, 1966 (Box 80, Folder 1316)
    - Educational Resources Project, Vermont Goddard College, 1956-1957 (Box 80, Folder 1317)
    - Educational Services Inc. - General Program, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 1318)
    - Education Services Inc. - New Curriculum, 1965 (Box 80, Folder 1319)
    - Haaren High School, 1971 (Box 80, Folder 1320)
    - Haaren High School - Richard Maize, old classrooms (Box 80, Folder 1321)
    - Hamilton College, "Teaching Machine", 1959 (Box 80, Folder 1322)
    - Hampshire College, 1968 (Box 80, Folder 1323)
    - Harlem Preparatory School, 1970 (Box 80, Folder 1324)
    - Harvard Graduate School of Education, 1964 (Box 80, Folder 1325)
    - Journalism Fellowship Recipients, 1966 (Box 80, Folder 1326)
    - Know College - Management Training Programs for Presidents, Deans, and Business Managers of Small Colleges, 1964 (Box 80, Folder 1327)
    - Lay Readers - Educational Testing Service, 1960 (Box 80, Folder 1328)
    - Leadership Development Project, New Mexico and South Carolina High Schools (Box 80, Folder 1329)
    - Locally Administered School Districts - Ocean Hill, Brownsville, from New York Times, 1968 May (Box 80, Folder 1330)
    - Nashville School Improvement Program, 1965 (Box 80, Folder 1331)
    - National Bureau of Economic Research, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 1332)
    - National Education Association - Experiment in Instructional Procedures, 1959 (Box 81, Folder 1333)
    - National Merit Scholarship Corporation, 1965 (Box 81, Folder 1334)
    - Negro Colleges - United Negro College Fund (UNCF), 1968 (Box 81, Folder 1335)
    - New College, Sarasota Florida, 1968 (Box 81, Folder 1336)
    - Northeastern Illinois University, Chicago, 1971 (Box 81, Folder 1337)
    - Norwalk Board of Education, Comprehensive Effort to Improve Elementary and Secondary School Programs, 1963 (Box 81, Folder 1338)
      Related Materials
      See also Ford Foundation grant 06200153 (PA62-153), Norwalk Board Of Education.
    - Oklahoma State University Experimental Program with Recent High School Dropouts, 1964 (Box 81, Folder 1339)
    - Open Classroom, New York City, 1971 (Box 81, Folder 1340)
    - Parkway Schools, "Schools Without Walls", 1969 (Box 81, Folder 1341)
    - Problems of the Library, Council on Library Resources, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 1342)
    - Project opportunity, Charlotte, North Carolina, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 1343)
    - Public School Reform, 1969 (Box 81, Folder 1344)
    - Rocky Mountain Area Project for Small High Schools, 1960 (Box 81, Folder 1345)
    - San Francisco Educational Fund - Mini grant programs for improving teaching and learning at school sties, 1984 (Box 81, Folder 1346)
      See also Ford Foundation grant 08250611 (PA82-611), San Francisco Education Fund.
    - Secondary Schools, 1974 (Box 81, Folder 1347)
    - "Schools and the Democratic Environment" film stills, Danforth and Ford Foundation conference, 1969 (Box 81, Folder 1348)
    - Shaw University, Raleigh, North Carolina, 1968 (Box 81, Folder 1349)
    - Southern Education Report - misc. photographs of schools, 1968 (Box 81, Folder 1350)
    - Strengthen Small Schools, Catskill Area and Rocky Mountain Area, 1960 (Box 81, Folder 1351)
    - Teaching with Computers - Elementary Curricula (RCA), 1968 (Box 81, Folder 1352)
    - Tutorial Community Project, Los Angeles Schools, 1974 (Box 81, Folder 1353)
    - Universities, 1950s-1960s (Box 81, Folder 1354)
    - University of Wisconsin - urban Extension Program, press release photographs, 1962 February 18 (Box 82, Folder 1355)
    - Virginia Kerns - Women's' Studies Doctoral program, Woodrow Wilson National fellowship, 1974 (Box 82, Folder 1356)
    - Vocational Education, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 1357)
    - Vocational Education press release - Harry Ells High School, Richmond CA, 1963 June 9 (Box 82, Folder 1358)
    - Western States Small Schools Project, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 1359)
    - Women's' Action Alliance - Men in the Nurturing Role, 1975 (Box 82, Folder 1360)
  - Educational Television (ETV), 3_4
    - Educational Television, 1950s-1960s (Box 82, Folder 1361, 1362, 1363)
    - Awards Panel - Awards given to 13 public TV stations and 4 public TV networks, 1968 (Box 82, Folder 1364)
    - "The 21 Inch Classroom" - Boston, MA, 1967 (Box 82, Folder 1365)
    - Chelsea Closed-Circuit TV Project, 1958 (Box 82, Folder 1366)
    - Chicago City College TV Station, WTTW, 1966 (Box 82, Folder 1367)
    - Continental Classroom, Coast to Coast Course in College Physics, 1959-1960 (Box 82, Folder 1368)
    - Hollywood Television Theatre, 1974 (Box 82, Folder 1369)
    - Midwest Airborne Educational Television Program, 1960-1966 (Box 83, Folder 1370)
    - Public Broadcasting Laboratory Series, 1967 (Box 83, Folder 1371)
    - TV/Radio Workshop - Omnibus, 1950s (Box 83, Folder 1372)
    - Washington County, Maryland (Hagerstown) - Use of closed Circuit television in schools, 1959 (Box 83, Folder 1373)
    - WGBH, Boston MA - "Science Reporter", 1966 (Box 83, Folder 1374)
    - WQED/WQEX, Pittsburgh, PA, 1966 (Box 83, Folder 1375)
  - Humanities and the Arts (H&A), 3_5
    - All Children's Theater, "The Trip" by Stephen Schwartz, 1983-1984 (Box 83, Folder 1376)
    - All Children's Theater, "The Trip" by Stephen Schwartz, set pieces and drawings, 1983-1984 (Box 83, Folder 1377)
    - Alley Theater, 1962-1969 (Box 83, Folder 1378)
    - American Conservatory Theatre, 1974 (Box 83, Folder 1379)
    - American Federation of Arts, New Theatre Design (Box 83, Folder 1380)
      See also Ford Foundation grant 06100261 (PA61-261), The American Federation Of Arts, Inc.
    - American Federation of Arts - Retrospective Art Show, 1959 (Box 83, Folder 1381)
    - American Indian Repertory Troupe, 1972 (Box 83, Folder 1382)
    - American School of Classical Studies, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 1383, 1384)
    - Archaeology Grants - University of Pennsylvania, 1968 (Box 84, Folder 1385)
    - Arena Stage, 1962 (Box 84, Folder 1386, 1387)
      George de Vincent photography
    - Artists in Residence, 1964 (Box 84, Folder 1388)
    - Artists in Residence - Germany (Box 84, Folder 1389)
    - Athens Drama Society / Greek Art Theatre, 1970 (Box 84, Folder 1390)
    - Ballet, 1950s-1960s (Box 84, Folder 1391)
    - Ballet - Pennsylvania Ballet Company, 1392 (Box 84, Folder 1392)
    - Ballet - Pennsylvania, Utah, Joffery NY, 1968 (Box 84, Folder 1393)
    - Barbara Hunt Associates, 1965 (Box 85, Folder 1394)
    - Brooklyn Museum, Catalog and Exhibit, John Paul Jones, 1963 (Box 85, Folder 1395)
    - Center for Southern Folklore, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 1396)
    - Children's' Art Carnival, Harlem, NYC, Museum of Modern Art, 1969 (Box 85, Folder 1397)
    - City Center, Joffrey Ballet, New York (Box 85, Folder 1398)
    - City Center of Music and drama, Inc - Production of Original Operas by Americans (Box 85, Folder 1399)
      See also Ford Foundation grant 06100218 (PA61-218), City Center of Music and Drama, Inc.
    - Cleveland Playhouse Touring Repertory Company, 1961 (Box 85, Folder 1400)
      See also Ford Foundation grant 05700402 (PA57-402), The Play House.
    - Connecticut Opera, 1969 (Box 85, Folder 1401)
    - Dallas Symphony Orchestra, 1966-1969 (Box 85, Folder 1402)
    - Dance Theater of Harlem (Box 85, Folder 1403, Box 135, Folder 1967)
    - Denver Symphony Orchestra, 1966 (Box 85, Folder 1404)
    - Detroit Symphony Orchestra, 1969 (Box 85, Folder 1405)
    - East-West Players, 1969 (Box 85, Folder 1406)
    - Ethnomusicology Institute, University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA) - Japanese Dancing (Box 85, Folder 1407)
    - Feld New Ballet School, New York, 1981 (Box 85, Folder 1408)
    - Fellowship Program for Editors, Reporters, and Critics, 1964 (Box 85, Folder 1409)
    - Fellowship Program for Film Makers, 1964 (Box 85, Folder 1410)
      Grantees include: Kenneth Anger, Jordan Belson, James Blue, Bruce Conner, Carmen D'Avino, Daniel Drasin, Edmund Emshwiller, Hilary T. Harris, Helen Levitt, Kent Mackenzie, John R. McDermott, and Stanley Vanderbeek. See also Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) 06490199 (PA64-199), PROGRAM FOR FILM MAKERS.
    - Fellowship program for non-academic scholars in the creative arts (Studies in the Creative Arts), 1961 (Box 85, Folder 1411)
      See also Ford Foundation Project file D-22: Fellowship program for non-academic scholars in the creative arts (Studies in the Creative Arts); and Grant file 06090249 (PA60-249), Foundation-Administered Project (FAP), "PROGRAM FOR STUDIES INTHE CREATIVE ARTS".
    - Festival Casals, 1967 (Box 85, Folder 1412)
    - Henry Ford Centennial Library (Box 85, Folder 1413)
    - Free Southern Theater, 1969 (Box 85, Folder 1414)
    - Grants to Individual Authors, 1950s-1960s (Box 85, Folder 1415)
      Includes photographs of the following grantees: James Baldwin (Project file C-638; Grant PA59-121), Rachmael Ben-Avram (Project file C-622; Grant PA59-115), Saul Bellow (Project file C-638), E.E. Cummings (Project file C-638), John Harding (Project file C-623), Stanley Kunitz (Project file C-638), Bernard Malamud (Project file C-638), Flannery O?Connor (Project file C-638), Theodore Roethke (Project file C-638).
    - Grants to Individual Musical Artists, 1950s-1960s (Box 85, Folder 1416)
      Includes photographs of the following grantees: Elliott Carter (Project files C-918, C-621, D-499; Grants PA59-84, PA59-153, PA62-250, PA63-351), Paul Creston (Project files C-918, C-621; Grant PA59-153), Phyllis Curtin (Project file D-499; Grant PA59-152), Carlisle Floyd (Project file C-918 C-621; Grants PA56-14, PA59-153, PA60-118), Lukas Foss (Project files C-918, C-621; Grants PA59-153, PA69-610), Joseph Fuchs (Project file D-499; Grant PA59-152), Vittorio Giannini (Project file C-621; Grants PA59-84, PA59-152, PA59-153, PA60-118, PA62-4, PA62-250, PA63-513, PA66-79), Irene Jordan (Grant PA59-152, D-499), Leon Kirchner (Project files C-918, C-621; Grants PA59-153, 59-84, PA62-333, PA69-610, Seymour Lipkin (Project files C-621, D-499; Grants PA59-152, PA59-161), Chester Ludgin, William Masselos (Project files C-621, D-499; Grants PA59-152, PA59-157), Walter Piston (Project files C-918, C-621; Grants PA59-153, PA60-249), Michael Rabin (Project file D-499, C-621; Grants PA59-152, PA59-161), Leonard Rose (Project file C-621, D-499; Grants PA59-152, PA59-156, PA59-158), William Schuman (Project files C-621, C-918; Grants PA57-34, PA59-153, PA59-156, PA59-158), Harold Shapero (Project files C-621, C-918; Grant PA59-153), Ben Webber (Project file C-621, C-918; Grants PA59-153, PA59-163).
    - Grants to Individual Playwrights and Theater Directors, 1950s-1960s (Box 86, Folder 1417)
      Includes photographs of the following grantees: William Ball (Project file C-622, Grants PA59-115, PA60-118), Herbert Blau (Project file C-638, Grant PA59-115), Angus Bowmer (Project files C-401, C-622; Grants PA59-115, PA59-118, PA62-406), Kenneth Cameron (Project file C-623; Grant PA58-294), Phillip Pruneau (Project file C-623; Grant PA58-294), John Reich (Project files C-622, D-22Grants PA57-402, PA59-115, PA59-119, PA61-32, PA61-137), Alan Schneider (Project file C-622, C-623, C-918, D-22, D-553, Grants PA57-402, PA58-294, PA59-115, PA61-137, PA64-479), Nina Vance (Project files C-622, C-623, C-918, D-497, D-553; Grants PA57-402, PA59-115, 59-117, PA59-234, PA60-18, PA60-149 PA61-32, PA61-137, PA62-490, PA63-514).
    - Grants to Individual Visual Artists, 1950s-1960s (Box 86, Folder 1418, Box 135, Folder 1967)
      Includes photographs of the following grantees: Josef Albers (Project file C-620; Grants PA59-120, PA62-107), Cosmo Campoli (Project files C-620, D-496; Grant PA60-84), Conrad Marca-Relli (Project file C-620; Grant PA59-120), Reuben Nakian (Project file C-620; Grant PA59-120), Adja Yunkers (Project file C-620; Grants PA59-120, PA60-256, PA62-107).
    - Greek Art Theater, 1971 (Box 86, Folder 1419)
    - Greek Association for Contemporary Music (Box 86, Folder 1420)
      See also Ford Foundation grant 06800614 (PA68-614), Greek Association of Contemporary Music.
    - Greek Folk Dance and Songs Society, 1970 (Box 86, Folder 1421)
    - Chester Higgins Jr. (RENACA Photography Ltd.) - African photographs, 1973 (Box 86, Folder 1422)
      See also Foundation-Administered Projects (FAPs) 07290003 (PA72-3): FISCAL YEAR 1972 TRAVEL AND STUDY GRANTS, and 07390003 (PA73-3): FISCAL YEAR 1973 TRAVEL AND STUDY GRANTS, for material on Higgins' "photographic study of the Black man in America".
    - Indianapolis Symphony Orchestra, 1966 (Box 86, Folder 1423)
    - Individual Grants-In-Aid, 1960-1962 (Box 86, Folder 1424)
    - Institute of American Indian Arts, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 1425)
      See also Ford Foundation grant 07200162 (PA72-162), Bureau of Indian Affairs, "SUPPORT IN-SERVICE STAFF TRAINING AND IMPROVE STAFF-STUDENT COMMUNICATIONS AT THE INSTITUTE OF AMERICAN INDIAN ARTS".
    - Japanese Dance (Box 86, Folder 1426)
    - Librarians Conference, Bowdoin College, 1966 (Box 86, Folder 1427)
    - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, 1966 (Box 86, Folder 1428)
    - Los Angeles Philharmonic Association, 1978 (Box 86, Folder 1429)
    - La Mama Theater and Open Theater, 1968 (Box 86, Folder 1430)
    - Manhattan School of Music, 1965 (Box 86, Folder 1431)
    - Metropolitan Opera Association (Box 86, Folder 1432)
    - Miami Opera Guild, 1967 (Box 86, Folder 1433)
    - Modern Dance, 1960s-1970s (Box 87, Folder 1434, 1435)
      Misc. general photographs. Includes Merce Cunningham, Murray Louis, Nikolais Dance Theater, and Paul Taylor Dance Company.
    - Mummers Theater (Box 87, Folder 1436)
    - Nelson Gallery, Kansas City, MO, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1437)
    - New England Opera Theater Company, 1958 (Box 87, Folder 1438)
    - New Orleans Philharmonic Symphony Orchestra, 1966-1967 (Box 87, Folder 1439)
    - New York Philharmonic, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 1440)
    - New York Pro Musica, 1969 (Box 87, Folder 1441)
    - New York Studio School, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1442)
    - Opera Guild of Greater Miami, 1964-1966 (Box 87, Folder 1443)
    - Opera Society of Washington, 1963-1966 (Box 87, Folder 1444)
    - Playwrights and Producing Theaters, Josh Greenfeld, Arena Stage, 1959 (Box 87, Folder 1445)
    - Poets and Writers at Residence in Theaters, 1964 (Box 87, Folder 1446)
    - Program for Concert Soloists, 1964 (Box 87, Folder 1447)
    - Program for Opera Singers, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 1448)
    - Purchases of works by American Artists, 1962 (Box 87, Folder 1449)
    - Roberson Center, Bridgehampton, NY (Box 87, Folder 1450)
    - Roswell Museum and Art Center - Fletcher Martin (Box 87, Folder 1451)
    - Seattle Symphony Orchestra, 1966 (Box 87, Folder 1452)
    - St. Louis Symphony Society, 1966 (Box 87, Folder 1453)
    - St. Paul Chamber Orchestra, College Residency Program (Box 87, Folder 1454)
    - Santa Fe Opera House, 1965-1969 (Box 87, Folder 1454A, Box 135, Folder 1967)
    - Stratford Shakespearean Festival of Canada, 1964 (Box 87, Folder 1455)
    - Strengthening of Resident Theater, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 1456, Box 135, Folder 1967)
    - Su Teatro, "Chicano 101", 1993 (Box 87, Folder 1457)
      Photographs used in the Spring 1993 'Ford Foundation Report' newsletter.
    - Symphony of the New World, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1458)
    - Tamarind Lithography Workshop, 1965 (Box 88, Folder 1459)
    - Young Audiences Inc., 1960s (Box 88, Folder 1460)
  - International Affairs (IA), 3_6
    - Agricultural Development Council, English Language Education, 1964 (Box 88, Folder 1461)
    - Athens College, Greece, 1959 (Box 88, Folder 1462)
    - Athenian Agora, 1965 (Box 88, Folder 1463)
    - Atlantic College, General Support for the College in Wales, 1963 (Box 88, Folder 1464)
    - Australian National University, 1963 (Box 88, Folder 1465)
    - University of Bologna, Graduate School in Administrative Sciences (Box 88, Folder 1466)
    - Common Market Studies, 1962 (Box 88, Folder 1467)
    - Congress for Cultural Freedom - Free Hungarian Orchestra, 1958 (Box 88, Folder 1468)
    - European Institute of Business Administration, Development of International Aspects of its Training and Research Programs (Box 88, Folder 1469)
      See also Ford Foundation grant 06100016 (PA61-16), European Institute of Business Administration.
    - European Organization for Nuclear Research (CERN), 1959 (Box 88, Folder 1470)
      See also Ford Foundation grant 05600241 (PA56-241), European Organization for Nuclear Research (CERN).
    - Free University of Berlin, 1958 (Box 88, Folder 1471)
    - Friedrich Ebert Foundation - Increase German participation, 1961 (Box 88, Folder 1472)
    - Inter American Press Association (IAPA) Technical Center, Strengthening of Democratic Press in Latin America, 1964 (Box 88, Folder 1473)
    - Institute of Advances Studies, 1964 (Box 88, Folder 1474)
    - Institute of Modern History, Academia Sinica, Nanking, Tapai, Taiwan, 1966 (Box 88, Folder 1475)
    - International Association of Students in Economic And Commercial Sciences, 1963 (Box 88, Folder 1476)
    - International Christian University, Tokyo, Japan, 1965 (Box 88, Folder 1477)
    - International Christian University, Graduate School of Public Administration, Japan, 1963 (Box 88, Folder 1478)
    - International Institute for Social History, 1960 (Box 88, Folder 1479)
    - International Labor Organization - International Training Course for Developing Countries, 1963 (Box 88, Folder 1480)
    - International Press Institute, Training of Journalists in Africa, 1964 (Box 88, Folder 1481)
    - International Schools Foundation, 1960 (Box 88, Folder 1482)
    - Johns Hopkins University, Bologna Center, 1965 (Box 88, Folder 1483)
    - Joint Program for Nuclear Studies, Austria, 1960 (Box 88, Folder 1484)
    - Kyoto University - center of Southeastern Studies, Exchange of Physicists by Research Institute of Fundamental Physics, 1963 (Box 88, Folder 1485)
    - National Union for the Struggle Against Illiteracy (UNLA), Italy, 1958 (Box 88, Folder 1486)
    - Organization for European Economic Cooperation, 1960 (Box 89, Folder 1487)
    - Oxford University - building Restoration Fund (Box 89, Folder 1488)
    - Political and Economic Planning (PEP), 1962 (Box 89, Folder 1489)
    - Salzburg Seminar in American Studies, 1961-1965 (Box 89, Folder 1490)
    - Swiss Friends of Angola - Training of Angolan students in Switzerland, 1962 (Box 89, Folder 1491)
    - United Nations, International School, 1966 (Box 89, Folder 1492)
    - University of London - Pitman Initial Teaching Alphabet, 1964 (Box 89, Folder 1493)
    - University of London, London School of Economics and Political Sciences - Graduate Course in Demography, 1965 (Box 89, Folder 1494)
    - University of Naples - Development of Italian Center of Advanced Training and Research in Agricultural Economics (Box 89, Folder 1495)
  - International Division (ID), 3_7
    - Agricultural Research Institutes (Box 89, Folder 1496)
    - Arid Lands - Lebanon, 1969 (Box 89, Folder 1497)
    - AURA - Cerro Tololo Inter-American Observatory, Chile, 1969 (Box 89, Folder 1498)
    - Chapingo - National School of Agriculture, Mexico, 1968 (Box 89, Folder 1499)
    - China, the United Nations, and United States Policy, A Report of the National Policy Panel, Reports 1-2, 1966-1967 (Box 89, Folder 1500)
    - International Maize and Wheat Improvement Center (CIMMYT), 1966 (Box 89, Folder 1501)
    - International Maize and Wheat Improvement Center (CIMMYT) - UNESCO Kalinga Prize, 1970 (Box 89, Folder 1502)
    - Columbia University - African Law Center (Box 89, Folder 1503)
    - East Pakistan Small Industries Corporation, 1969 (Box 89, Folder 1504)
    - International Crops Research Institute for Semi-Arid Tropics (ICRISAT), India - Visit by Ford Foundation Officers McGeorge Bundy and Harry E. Wilhelm, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 1505)
    - India - Water Development, 1960s (Box 89, Folder 1506)
    - International Rice Research Institute (IRRI), Philippines, 1962-1966 (Box 89, Folder 1507)
    - Johns Hopkins Center for International Studies, Washington DC, 1967-1968 (Box 90, Folder 1508)
    - Meking Delta, Thailand, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 1509)
    - National Institute of Agricultural Investigation, Mexico, 1963 (Box 90, Folder 1510)
    - PEN International, 34th International Congress - New York, "The Writer As Independent Spirit", 1966 (Box 90, Folder 1511)
    - "Years of famine/years of plenty" by Wayne Swegle, photographs, 1971-1974 (Box 90, Folder 1512, 1513)
    - University of Malaya, 1964 (Box 90, Folder 1514)
    - Yugoslavia, Economic Development, United Nations (Box 90, Folder 1515)
  - International Training and Research (ITR), 3_8
    - American Institute of Indian Studies, 1964 (Box 90, Folder 1516)
    - Boston University - Summer Orientation Seminar for Foreign Students, 1963 (Box 90, Folder 1517)
    - Columbia University - International Studies Program in Advanced International Reporting, 1964 (Box 90, Folder 1518)
    - Cornell University - International Agricultural Development (Box 90, Folder 1519)
    - George Washington University - Institute of Sino-Soviet Studies, 1964 (Box 90, Folder 1520)
    - Gettysburg College - Non-Western Studies - Faculty International Studies Program, 1963 (Box 90, Folder 1521)
    - Inter-University Program of travel to U.S.S.R, 1959 (Box 90, Folder 1522)
    - Latin American Studies, 1963 (Box 90, Folder 1523)
    - New York University - Research on Legal Aspects of International Rivers, 1954 (Box 90, Folder 1524)
    - Northwestern University, 1966 (Box 90, Folder 1525)
    - Purdue University - International Studies - Agricultural Extension, 1964 (Box 90, Folder 1526)
    - Stanford University - Education Planning for Developing Countries, 1964 (Box 90, Folder 1527)
    - Stanford University - Inter-University Language Program, Center of Japanese Studies in Tokyo (Box 90, Folder 1528)
    - Stanford University - International Studies Program, 1963 (Box 90, Folder 1529)
    - Syracuse University - Strengthening of International Studies, 1963 (Box 90, Folder 1530)
    - Texas Agricultural and Mechanical University -Training for Overseas, 1964 (Box 90, Folder 1531)
    - Transfer of Foreign Area Fellowship program to SSRC and ACLS, 1962 (Box 90, Folder 1532)